

Personal information



ophelia.m.aguilar@gmail.com

(+46)760-070035

Vasavägen 24

Solna, Stockholm

Skills

C#

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Java

Kotlin

React.js

React Native

Swift

UI

UX

Figma

UML Scrum

Vue.js

Tailwind CSS

Languages

Swedish - Native

English - Fluent

Social media





Ophelia Aguilar

About me

I am a 25-year-old programming student looking for new opportunities in Stockholm. I am currently studying app development remotely at Stockholms Tekniska Institut and will graduate this spring.

My big passions are gaming and programming, I also have an interest in people and have many years of experience in the service industry.

I am hardworking, curious, and open to everything new. I would like the opportunity to learn and contribute by working together with you.

Education

App Development

2021 - 2023

Stockholms Tekniska Institut

The studies are mainly focused on mobile app development. I've also studied project management, UX, UI, and how to build prototypes in Figma.

2020 - 2021 Programming

Kvinnofolkhögskolan

I studied the fundamentals of programming. I frequently used UML for projects and used Scrum to sufficiently plan a wedding with a group of classmates.

Society & Behavioral Science 2015 - 2016

Birkagårdens Folkhögskola

2013 - 2015 Art & Design

Cybergymnasiet

Work experience

Programming Intern

January 2023 - April 2023

I mainly focused on building and improving the company website and design, using React.js, Vue.js, Tailwind CSS and Figma.

Warehouse Worker April 2022 - September 2022

Mopedrenovering

Programming Intern April 2021 - May 2021

Albert Schapiro Autonomo

I mainly focused on building and improving the company website, using React.js

February 2020 - July 2020 Claims Adjuster

AmTrust Insurance Services Sweden

Sales Advisor October 2019 - January 2020

H&M

Customer Service Employee & Insurance Agent **August 2018 - April 2019**

mySafety Försäkringar

Additional work experience **July 2016 - August 2018**

I worked as a Barista and Restaurant Staff at MAX Hamburgare, Espresso House, and Burger